A Guide to the Island Resources Foundation records FA1200
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects and Occasional Papers, 1894-1895, 1946, 1956, 1961-1964, 1968-2016; 3; 33.3 Cubic Feet 85 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, and 1 flat file folder
  - #149, Cambodia Coastal Zone Management Training, Budget and Terms of Reference, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1365)
  - #149, Cambodia Coastal Zone Management Training, Correspondence with John McEachern, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1366)
  - #149, Cambodia Coastal Zone Management Training, Miscellaneous Documentation, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1367)
  - #150, UN Development Programme (UNDP), GEF Biodiversity, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 119, Folder 1368)
  - #150, UN Development Programme (UNDP), GEF Biodiversity, Background Information, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1369)
  - #150, UN Development Programme (UNDP), GEF Biodiversity, Correspondence with UNDP, 1998-1999 (Box 119, Folder 1370)
  - #150, UN Development Programme (UNDP), GEF Biodiversity, Antigua Projects, Environmental Awareness Group, 1997-2001 (Box 119, Folder 1371)
  - #150, UN Development Programme (UNDP), GEF Biodiversity, Nevis Project, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society, 1997-2000 (Box 119, Folder 1372)
  - #150, UN Development Programme (UNDP), GEF Biodiversity, St. Kitts Project, St. Christopher Heritage Society, 1997-1999 (Box 119, Folder 1373)
  - #151, Information Manager for Inter-American Strategy for Participation (ISP) (Organization for American States (OAS)), Contract, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1374)
  - #151, Information Manager for Inter-American Strategy for Participation (ISP) (Organization for American States (OAS)), Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1375)
  - #151, Information Manager for Inter-American Strategy for Participation (ISP) (Organization for American States (OAS)), Correspondence with OAS, 1997-1998 (Box 119, Folder 1376)
  - #152, Library Relocation to British Virgin Islands, Correspondence with Community College, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1377)
  - #153, Trellis Bay, British Virgin Islands, Environmental Impact Assessment, Proposals and Contract, 1998 (Box 119, Folder 1378)
  - #153, Trellis Bay, British Virgin Islands, Environmental Impact Assessment, Background Information, 1998 (Box 119, Folder 1379)
  - #153, Trellis Bay, British Virgin Islands, Environmental Impact Assessment, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1998 (Box 119, Folder 1380)
  - #153, Trellis Bay, British Virgin Islands, Environmental Impact Assessment, Onions Bouchard and McCulloch and Smiths Core Correspondence, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 1381)
  - #153, Trellis Bay, British Virgin Islands, Beef Island, Environmental Impact Assessment, 1998 (Box 120, Folder 1382)
  - #153, Trellis Bay, British Virgin Islands, Beef Island, Environmental Impact Assessment, Photographs, 2000 (Box 192, Folder 2214)
  - #154, Mapping Threatened Virgin Islands Watersheds, Proposal and Memorandum of Agreement, 1997-2000 (Box 120, Folder 1383)
  - #154, Mapping Threatened Virgin Islands Watersheds, Internal Correspondence and Personnel, 1998-2002 (Box 120, Folder 1384)
  - #154, Mapping Threatened Virgin Islands Watersheds, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 120, Folder 1385)
  - #154, Mapping Threatened Virgin Islands Watersheds, Experts Panel Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 120, Folder 1386)
  - #154, Mapping Threatened Virgin Islands Watersheds, Correspondence with VI Government Agencies, 1998-2000, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 1387)
  - #154, Mapping Threatened Virgin Islands Watersheds, Reports, 2002 (Box 120, Folder 1388)
  - #155, Antigua Biodiversity Enabling Activities, Proposal and Correspondence with Government, re: Contract/Project, 1998-2001 (Box 120, Folder 1389)
  - #155, Antigua Biodiversity Enabling Activities, Documentation and Miscellaneous Information, 1998-1999 (Box 120, Folder 1390)
  - #155, Antigua Biodiversity Enabling Activities, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2000 (Box 120, Folder 1391)
  - #155, Antigua Biodiversity Enabling Activities, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 120, Folder 1392)
  - #155, Antigua Biodiversity Enabling Activities, Stocktaking, Final Report, 1999 (Box 120, Folder 1393)
  - #156, Virgin Islands 305(b) Report, Proposal, Contract, and Related Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 120, Folder 1394)
  - #156, Virgin Islands 305(b) Report, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 120, Folder 1395)
  - #156, Virgin Islands 305(b) Report, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 1396)
  - #156, Virgin Islands 305(b) Report, Correspondence with Department of Planning and Natural Resources, Other Government Agencies, 1998-2000 (Box 121, Folder 1397)
  - #156, Virgin Islands 305(b) Report, Report, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 1398)
  - #157, St. Thomas/St. John Mapping (The Nature Conservancy (TNC)), Proposal, Contract, TNC Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 121, Folder 1399)
  - #157, St. Thomas/St. John Mapping (The Nature Conservancy (TNC)), Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 1400)
  - #157, St. Thomas/St. John Mapping (The Nature Conservancy (TNC)), Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 121, Folder 1401)
  - #158, Caribbean Conservation History, Correspondence with Mukti Fund, 2001-2004 (Box 121, Folder 1402)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Proposal, 1999-2000 (Box 121, Folder 1403)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 121, Folder 1404)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999-2001, 2003 (Box 121, Folder 1405)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Correspondence with British Virgin Islands Partners, 2000-2003 (Box 121, Folder 1406)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Correspondence with Donor, 1999-2003 (Box 121, Folder 1407)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Legal Issues, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1408)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Ecosystem Report, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1409)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Ecosystem Report, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 1410)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Management Plan, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 1411-1412)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Assessment of the National, Regional, and International Laws and Treaties Governing the Role of the British Virgin Islands Parks Trust, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 1413)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, The Underwater World of Sandy Cay (Box 122, Folder 1414)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, The Underwater World of Sandy Cay-The Underwater World of Sandy Cay (Box 122, Folder 1414)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, The Underwater World of Sandy Cay-The Underwater World of Sandy Cay, VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11892)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Clips About Laurance Rockefeller (Box 122, Folder 1415)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Clips About Laurance Rockefeller-Clips About Laurance Rockefeller (Box 122, Folder 1415)
  - #160, Sandy Cay, Clips About Laurance Rockefeller, 2003; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 11893)
  - #161, Flood Hazard Mitigation Plan, Proposal and Contract, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 1416)
  - #161, Flood Hazard Mitigation Plan, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 1417)
  - #161, Flood Hazard Mitigation Plan, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 1418)
  - #161, Flood Hazard Mitigation Plan, Documentation, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 1419)
  - #161, Flood Hazard Mitigation Plan, Correspondence with Government Agencies, 2000-2002 (Box 122, Folder 1420)
  - #161, Flood Hazard Mitigation Plan, VITEMA (VI Territorial Emergency Management Agency), 2000 (Box 122, Folder 1421)
  - #161, Flood Hazard Mitigation Plan, VITEMA (VI Territorial Emergency Management Agency), 2000 (Box 123, Folder 1423)
  - #162, Tools for Watershed Management, Proposal and Contract, 2000-2002 (Box 123, Folder 1423)
  - #162, Tools for Watershed Management, Documents, Reports, Miscellaneous Information, 1999, 2001-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1424)
  - #162, Tools for Watershed Management, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1425)
  - #162, Tools for Watershed Management, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 123, Folder 1426)
  - #162, Tools for Watershed Management, Terms of Reference with Conservation Data Centers-University of the Virgin Islands, 2002-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1427)
  - #162, Tools for Watershed Management, Engorgement Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 123, Folder 1428)
  - #163, Coral Manual Translation, Grant Award Documentation, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 1429)
  - #163, Coral Manual Translation, Internal Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 123, Folder 1430)
  - #163, Coral Manual Translation, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 123, Folder 1431)
  - #163, Coral Reef Monitoring Manual, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 1432)
  - #163, Coral Reef Monitoring Manual, Spanish Translation, 2001 (Box 124, Folder 1433)
  - #164, UN Environment Programme (UNEP), Regional Office for Latin American and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environmental Outlook (GEO) 3, Proposal and Contract, 2000-2001 (Box 124, Folder 1434)
  - #164, UN Environment Programme (UNEP), Regional Office for Latin American and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environmental Outlook (GEO) 3, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 124, Folder 1435)
  - #164, UN Environment Programme (UNEP), Regional Office for Latin American and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environmental Outlook (GEO) 3, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 124, Folder 1436)
  - #164, UN Environment Programme (UNEP), Regional Office for Latin American and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environmental Outlook (GEO) 3, Correspondence with UNEP, 2000-2003 (Box 124, Folder 1437)
  - #165, Elkhorn Coral Analysis, Proposal and Contract, 2000-2001 (Box 124, Folder 1438)
  - #165, Elkhorn Coral Analysis, External Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 124, Folder 1439)
  - #165, Elkhorn Coral Analysis, Report, 2002 (Box 124, Folder 1440)
  - #166, US Virgin Islands Marine Park Planning, Proposal and Contract, 2001 (Box 124, Folder 1441)
  - #166, US Virgin Islands Marine Park Planning, Background Documentation, 2001-2002 (Box 124, Folder 1442)
  - #166, US Virgin Islands Marine Park Planning, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 124, Folder 1443)
  - #166, US Virgin Islands Marine Park Planning, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 124, Folder 1444)
  - #166, US Virgin Islands Marine Park Planning, University of Virgin Islands, Government Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 124, Folder 1445)
  - #166, US Virgin Islands Marine Park Planning, Report, 2002 (Box 125, Folder 1446-1147)
  - #166, US Virgin Islands Marine Park Planning, Report-MPA Resource Description & References & Maps, 2002 August 31 (Box 125, Folder 1446)
  - #167, World Resources Institute Reefs at Risk, Contract, 2002 (Box 125, Folder 1448)
  - #167, World Resources Institute Reefs at Risk, Internal Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 125, Folder 1449)
  - #167, World Resources Institute Reefs at Risk, Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 125, Folder 1450)
  - #168, Project Phoenix, Internal Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 125, Folder 1451)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Proposal and Contract, 2002 (Box 125, Folder 1452-1453)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Government, 2002-2005 (Box 125, Folder 1454)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Sub-Contract with Conservation Data Centers/Water Resources Research/University of the Virgin Islands, 2002-2003 (Box 125, Folder 1455)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 125, Folder 1456)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 126, Folder 1457-1458)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, University of the Virgin Islands, Conservation Data Centers Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 126, Folder 1459-1460)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Reports to Government, 2002-2005 (Box 126, Folder 1461)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Documentation, 2003-2004 (Box 126, Folder 1462-1463)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Documentation-Wetlands Inventory, DPNR Final, 2004 October 28 (Box 126, Folder 1462)
  - #169, Virgin Islands Wetlands Survey, Final Report, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 1464)
  - #170, British Virgin Islands Legislation Update, Memorandum of Understanding, 2001-2001 (Box 126, Folder 1465)
  - #170, British Virgin Islands Legislation Update, National Trust and Government Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 127, Folder 1466)
  - #170, British Virgin Islands Legislation Update, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 127, Folder 1467)
  - #170, British Virgin Islands Legislation Update, Report, Meghan E. Jeans, 2002 (Box 127, Folder 1468)
  - #171, Sandy Cay Rat Eradication, Proposal and Donor Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 127, Folder 1469)
  - #171, Sandy Cay Rat Eradication, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 127, Folder 1470)
  - #171, Sandy Cay Rat Eradication, British Virgin Islands Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 127, Folder 1471)
  - #171, Sandy Cay Rat Eradication, Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 127, Folder 1472)
  - #172, Coral Reef Ecosystem Studies, University of Puerto Rico, Proposal, 2002 (Box 127, Folder 1473)
  - #172, Coral Reef Ecosystem Studies, University of Puerto Rico, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2002-2006 (Box 127, Folder 1473)
  - #172, Coral Reef Ecosystem Studies, University of Puerto Rico, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 127, Folder 1474)
  - #172, Coral Reef Ecosystem Studies, University of Puerto Rico, Project Partners Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 127, Folder 1475)
  - #172, Coral Reef Ecosystem Studies, University of Puerto Rico, Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 127, Folder 1476)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Proposal, 2000-2003 (Box 127, Folder 1477)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 127, Folder 1478)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 128, Folder 1479)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Correspondence with Donor and Representatives, 1991, 2003-2005 (Box 128, Folder 1480)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Quarterly Progress Reports to Donor, 2003-2005 (Box 128, Folder 1481)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Program Advisory Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 128, Folder 1482)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Workshops and Seminars, 2004 (Box 128, Folder 1483)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Legislation Component, Barbara Lausche, 2001, 2003-2005 (Box 128, Folder 1484)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2004 (Box 128, Folder 1485)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Correspondence with H. Lavity Stoutt Community College, 2003-2004 (Box 128, Folder 1486)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Correspondence with Jost Van Dykes (BVI) Preservation Society, 2004-2005 (Box 129, Folder 1487)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Correspondence with National Parks Trust, 2003-2005 (Box 129, Folder 1488-1489)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Press Releases and Other Public Relations Materials, 2001-2004, 2009 (Box 129, Folder 1490)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Miscellaneous Documentation, Year One, 2002-2004 (Box 129, Folder 1491)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Miscellaneous Documentation, Year Two, 2004-2005 (Box 129, Folder 1492)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Documents for Distribution, 2004-2005 (Box 129, Folder 1493)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Documents for Distribution-Jost Van Dykes (JVD) and Sandy Cay Pictures, 2005 February 22-23 (Box 129, Folder 1493)
  - #174, Sandy Cay II, Documents for Distribution-Sandy Cay (BVI) Field Trips, 2004 February (Box 129, Folder 1493)
  - #175, CDERA (Caribbean Disaster Emergency Response Agency) Institutional Review, Proposal and Contract, 2003 (Box 129, Folder 1494)
  - #175, CDERA (Caribbean Disaster Emergency Response Agency) Institutional Review, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 129, Frame 1495)
  - #175, CDERA (Caribbean Disaster Emergency Response Agency) Institutional Review, Internal Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 129, Folder 1496)
  - #175, CDERA (Caribbean Disaster Emergency Response Agency) Institutional Review, Correspondence with CDERA, 2003-2004 (Box 130, Folder 1497)
  - #175, CDERA (Caribbean Disaster Emergency Response Agency) Institutional Review, Grenada, Final Report, 2004 (Box 130, Folder 1498)
  - #175, CDERA (Caribbean Disaster Emergency Response Agency) Institutional Review, Barbados, Final Report, 2004 (Box 130, Folder 1499)
  - #176, Virgin Islands Environmental Resources Directory, Proposal and Contract, 2003-2004 (Box 130, Folder 1500)
  - #176, Virgin Islands Environmental Resources Directory, Internal Correspondence, 2004-2007 (Box 130, Frame 1501)
  - #176, Virgin Islands Environmental Resources Directory, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2005 (Box 130, Folder 1502)
  - #176, Virgin Islands Environmental Resources Directory, Quarterly Reports to Department of Planning and Natural Resources, 2004-2005 (Box 130, Folder 1503)
  - #176, Virgin Islands Environmental Resources Directory, Government Correspondence, 2004-2006 (Box 130, Folder 1504)
  - #176, Virgin Islands Environmental Resources Directory, Miscellaneous Documentation, 2205 (Box 130, Folder 1505)
  - #177, Terrestrial Survey, Dolphin Cove, St. Thomas, Proposal, 2004 (Box 130, Folder 1506)
  - #177, Terrestrial Survey, Dolphin Cove, St. Thomas, Internal Correspondence, 2004 (Box 130, Folder 1507)
  - #177, Terrestrial Survey, Dolphin Cove, St. Thomas, Correspondence with Client, 2004-2005 (Box 130, Folder 1508)
  - #177, Terrestrial Survey, Dolphin Cove, St. Thomas, Documentation, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 131, Folder 1509)
  - #177, Terrestrial Survey, Dolphin Cove, St. Thomas, Documentation-Dolphin Cove, Final Report (Box 131, Folder 1509)
  - #178, Sanctuary Cove Survey, Frenchman's Bay, St. Thomas, Proposal, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 1510)
  - #178, Sanctuary Cove Survey, Frenchman's Bay, St. Thomas, Internal Correspondence, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 1511)
  - #178, Sanctuary Cove Survey, Frenchman's Bay, St. Thomas, Correspondence with Client, 2004-2006 (Box 131, Folder 1512)
  - #178, Sanctuary Cove Survey, Frenchman's Bay, St. Thomas, Documentation, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 1513)
  - #178, Sanctuary Cove Survey, Frenchman's Bay, St. Thomas, Documentation-Sanctuary Cove, Final Report (Box 131, Folder 1513)
  - #179, Botany Bay, US Virgin Islands Survey, Proposal and Contract, 2004-2005 (Box 131, Folder 1514)
  - #179, Botany Bay, US Virgin Islands Survey, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 1515)
  - #179, Botany Bay, US Virgin Islands Survey, Internal Correspondence and Personnel, 2004-2006 (Box 131, Folder 1516)
  - #179, Botany Bay, US Virgin Islands Survey, Correspondence with Client, 2004-2006 (Box 131, Folder 1517)
  - #179, Botany Bay, US Virgin Islands Survey, Reports and Documentation, 2004-2006 (Box 131, Folder 1518)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Proposal, 2004-2005 (Box 131, Folder 1519)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Personnel and Consultants, 2004-2005 (Box 131, Folder 1520)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2004-2007 (Box 131, Folder 1521)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Correspondence with British Virgin Islands Government, 2005-2006 (Box 131, Folder 1522)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Miscellaneous Information, 2004-2007 (Box 131, Folder 1522)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Correspondence with Client, 2004-2006 (Box 132, Folder 1523)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Internal Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 132, Folder 1524)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Beef Island Development Project Partners, 2004-2006 (Box 132, Folder 1525)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Progress Reports to Clients, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 1526)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Reports, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 1527)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Beef Island Scoping Report, Final, 2005 (Box 132, Folder 1528-1529)
  - #180, Beef Island Environmental Impact Assessment, Beef Island Scoping Report-Final-Beef Island Scoping Report, 2005 November 14 (Box 132, Folder 1528)
  - #181, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP)/Regional Office for Latin America and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environment Outlook (GEO), Contract, 2005-2010 (Box 132, Folder 1530)
  - #181, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP)/Regional Office for Latin America and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environment Outlook (GEO), Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2005-2008, 2010 (Box 133, Folder 1531)
  - #181, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP)/Regional Office for Latin America and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environment Outlook (GEO), Correspondence with UNEP, 2005-2010 (Box 133, Folder 1532)
  - #181, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP)/Regional Office for Latin America and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environment Outlook (GEO), Correspondence with UNEP-La Tierra Agrietada (Box 133, Folder 1532)
  - #181, United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP)/Regional Office for Latin America and the Caribbean (ROLAC), Global Environment Outlook (GEO), Internal Correspondence and Personnel, 2005-2010 (Box 133, Folder 1533)
  - #182, SPAW (Specially Protected Areas of Wildlife) Guidelines, Contract and Agreements, 2005 (Box 133, Folder 1534)
  - #182, SPAW (Specially Protected Areas of Wildlife) Guidelines, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 133, Folder 1535)
  - #182, SPAW (Specially Protected Areas of Wildlife) Guidelines, Partner Correspondence, 2005-2010 (Box 133, Folder 1536-1537)
  - #182, SPAW (Specially Protected Areas of Wildlife) Guidelines, UN Environment Programme (UNEP) and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2005-2009 (Box 133, Folder 1538)
  - #182, SPAW (Specially Protected Areas of Wildlife) Guidelines, Reports, 2006 (Box 133, Folder 1539)
  - #183, British Virgin Islands Conservation, Association of Reef Keepers (ARK), Sub-grants Awarded, 2006-2007 (Box 133, Folder 1540)
  - #183, British Virgin Islands Conservation, Association of Reef Keepers (ARK), Jost Van Dyke Wetlands Project, 2010, 2012, 2014, 2016 (Box 133, Folder 1541)
  - #183, British Virgin Islands Conservation, Association of Reef Keepers (ARK), Correspondence with ARK, 2005, 2010 (Box 134, Folder 1542)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Proposal, Donor Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 134, Folder 1543)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2005-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1544)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Jost Van Dyke Society, 2005-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1545)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, National Park Trust Correspondence, 2005-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1546-1547)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, British Virgin Islands Government Correspondence, 2005-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1548)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2005, 2007-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1549)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Donor Correspondence, 2007-2009 (Box 135, Folder 1550-1551)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Information, 2004, 2008 (Box 135, Folder 1552)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Information-The Official Handing Over Sandy Cay to the National Parks Trust, 2008 April 30-June 2 (Box 135, Folder 1552)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Information-Sandy Cay, Transfer Ceremony, 2008 May 1 (Box 135, Folder 1552)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Information-Public Eye 2008, Sandy Cay Transfer, 2008 April 24 (Box 135, Folder 1152)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Quarterly and Other Reports, 1971, 1974, 2006-2008 (Box 135, Folder 1553)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Documents, 1971, 1974, 2006-2008 (Box 135, Folder 1554)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Reports, 2007-2008 (Box 135, Folder 1555-1556)
  - #184, Sandy Cay III, Reports-Sandy Cay, Monitoring Manual, 2008 (Box 135, Folder 1556)
  - #185, Fish Bay Erosion Control, Proposal and Contract, 2005-2008, 2010 (Box 136, Folder 1557)
  - #185, Fish Bay Erosion Control, Personnel and Internal Correspondence, 2006-2008 (Box 136, Folder 1558)
  - #185, Fish Bay Erosion Control, External Correspondence, 2006-2008 (Box 136, Folder 1559)